

BHONE PYAE KO



+959968803109



bhoneko220@gmail.com



Thegon, Bago, Myanmar

ABOUT ME

I am a university-bound student specializing in Information Technology, with a strong focus on Software Development and Artificial Intelligence. I am dedicated to continuous learning and thrive on tackling challenging projects that deepen my technical skills and understanding.

EXPERIENCE

2017 - PRESENT

STORE CAHSIER

Aung Mobile

- Offer consumer goods packages to corporate and clients
- Packing consumer goods

• 2019 - 2020

PHONE SERVICES TECHNICIAN

Aung Mobile

- Selling phones to customers, providing online services
- Repairing phones with damaged parts

• 2024 - PRESENT

TECHNOLOGY DIRECTOR

The STEMSphere

- Leading tech setup for live classes and LMS integration in STEM projects
- Managing Technology Department

EDUCATION

• 2011-2020

B.E.H.S, THEGON

KG to Grade-9

• 2022 - 2024

ACADEMY SCHOOL

Grade-10 to Grade-11

• 2023 - 2024

ROYAL ACADEMIC INSTITUTE

GED (Grade 12)

EXPERTISE

- Web Development
- Creativity
- Negotiation Critical
- Thinking
- Leadership

LANGUAGE

- Burmese (Native)
- English (Upper Intermediate)
- Japanese (N₄)